Yes!
So, today is the second installment of
The second project of the same age group!
Yay! The second one!
I didn't think there would be a second project!
I'm so happy!
It's been over a year?
Yes! Yes!
Last year was so much fun!
I've always wanted to do it again, and I can't believe my wish came true so soon.
Thank you so much!
So today we are going to have a party at our villa!
So first of all, I would like to introduce you all to this beautiful villa!
Let's go!
I'll follow in single file!
Walk, walk, walk!
It's our villa!
Yes, you are all invited!
I'll be waiting for you.
Welcome back, I'm home.
I'm home.
Boom!
Wow!
That's great.
I'm coming in.
Excuse me.
Can you go?
I'm going to meet you!
The garden is very nice and sunny, and the wind is cool and refreshing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
It's amazing!
Look!
Isn't it amazing?
Two of them, even five of them in a row.
It's so long that it sticks out.
Wow!
He's measuring it.
It's going up. That's great.
Let's all sit down.
It's big enough to sit on.
Ready, set, go!
Yay!
It's so wide!
Lay down and watch TV.
Watch TV.
I'll give you... it's been a long time.
There's a lot to see at the fair.
You want to see this room?
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
Okay, so it's just the three of us in one bed when he's in the room.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Yes, a 9 a curler, isn't it?
Watch out for the stairs!
Hey, don't slip out of these.
Don't slip out of your slippers
I'm so excited!
It's great!
It gets a lot of sun.
Oh, wow.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's glowing.
This space is so lit up.
What? Where? Where?
Where? Where?
You saw it, didn't you?
What do you mean?
Back up.
Back up a little bit.
What? Almost there?
It's glowing so brightly.
Here's the list.
There it is.
Hmm?
Let's go.
It was so bright.
It looks like it could be right over there.
Go ahead.
What? The spotlight.
Spotlight.
Oh, that's nice.
I like it.
I can make ramen noodles.
melting just Small
Small
Body
See you later.
Good donation!
Isn't this amazing? I'm having so much fun with just this light.
It's not every day you meet a sci-fi guy who drinks at a beach house.
We can look down.
It's fun.
Wow!
I bet you can play music and stuff.
There's speakers, too.
It's amazing.
Oh my God!
It's like all of them.
There's more.
Here's another room.
Shall we go?
Okay, Saya, you'll go first this time.
I'll go first.
Thank you.
Matching.
Here.
Wow.
It's huge.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
The three of us slept in this bed, and the next day, the three of us will sleep in this bed.
That's great... a different bed every day.
This floor? Still that way.
Oh, wow! It's so big!
It's so big!
Light! Light!
There it is!
Oh, my God!
Here's the seal!
This way.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
Heligo!
How nice to see you ladies!
Oh!
There's a washing machine
Why?
They have a washing machine.
And...
I don't know what to do.
This way.
What, this one?
What's this?
What... what... what... what... what... what...
What the hell is going on?
Wait, wait, wait.
We'll take one of each here.
Right... on the third day...
Right here.
Great.
It's great.
Little kids will be so excited.
I'm so excited.
There's a little girl.
Let's go upstairs.
There's more up there.
That's great, isn't it?
That's great.
I can kind of see it now.
There's a staircase.
There are stairs.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
It's the third floor on the back.
Two is fine.
Here we go.
Two's good.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Two is good.
It's on the third floor.
Saiya.
There you go.
Saiya's on the third floor.
I saw that.
I saw it.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Amazing.
I can see the ocean.
It's so beautiful!
It's springtime!
Right?
I'll probably try to hold the main mountain.
It's Earth!
I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it
It's like this, it's like a race, but it's not in the garden.
Let's go to the main part of the first floor.
Let's go.
Yes, so we're in the garden.
Here we are.
And...
Here's the pool.
Look at that, let's go closer.
Let's go closer.
Mai-chan!
Don't push me.
Don't ever push it.
If you push this, you'll get hurt.
It's really serious.
Wait, what's this?
What is this?
Open it!
Wood!
The handle's made of wood.
It's not a sauna.
Sauna.
Oh, my God.
It's a sauna.
It's a real sauna.
Wow.
There's a water bath here.
That's great.
So it's all set up?
Does it have hot water?
There's hot water, too. Like an open-air bath.
Oh, I see.
That's what I'm talking about.
Let's take a rest.
Let's take a break.
Let's stand in line.
Let's get in line.
Come on.
Take a bath.
Oh, hey, I thought...
Ah.
That's nice.
Yay.
All right. All right.
Let's go next.
Let's go to the next one.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
Can we dance? Just this space.
Music video.
We could do a music video.
I'll try not to think that I like you.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Chillas.
Chillas?
Flickers.
Flickers?
fluttering
Oh, I don't know.
I think I'll go see him.
What, what, what, what?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got it.
I think I've lost them.
I don't know where they are.
Oh, something...
Right there.
Look right there.
I don't get it.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Welcome.
Is this the Sayana Democratic Emperor?
Yes, it is.
They welcomed us.
That's not how we use it.
He said the three of us should sleep together.
The three of us will sleep together.
So this is where we'll make ourselves at home.
They're sleeping.
Yay, yay, it's Gumi's annual girls' night out.
It's a girls' night out, and sometimes it works out.
We can do it.
So, the room tour is over!
It was so much fun!
It was amazing!
After the tour, we would like to have a second barbecue at a very nice place like this.
We are going to have our second barbecue
I'm looking forward to it!
It's a really nice place.
Let's feel like we're having a barbecue together!
Please watch the next video!
Bye bye!